<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BVM</string>




    <string-array name="Semesters">
        <item>Select Semester</item>
        <item>Semester 1</item>
        <item>Semester 2</item>
        <item>Semester 3</item>
        <item>Semester 4</item>
        <item>Semester 5</item>
        <item>Semester 6</item>
        <item>Semester 7</item>
        <item>Semester 8</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Subjects">
        <item>Select Subject</item>
        <item>Subject 1</item>
        <item>Subject 2</item>
        <item>Subject 3</item>
        <item>Subject 4</item>
        <item>Subject 5</item>
        <item>Subject 6</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="starttime">
        <item>Start</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>11</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="endtime">
        <item>End</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>11</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="HINT">ABCD</string>

    <string name="abc"> <font style='text-align:justify' color='black' size='20'>
  <b><font size='35'>BIRLA VISHVAKARMA MAHAVIDYALAYA</font></b> \n \n
     <font size='20'>   \u2022  A PREMIER INSTITUTION OF CVM \n
        \u2022  FOUNDED IN 194 \n
        \u2022  Motto: Work is Worship \n
        \u2022  First Approved by Government as grant-in-aid College \n
        \u2022  More than 20000 engineers Graduated. \n
        \u2022  Degrees offered – B.Tech., M.Tech. &amp; Ph.D. \n \n
        </font>

          <b><font size='25'>The starting days</font></b> \n
        The infrastructure of the college was generously designed for three year degree programme with an intake of 150 students every year. The main building (now known as A Block) had class rooms and laboratories. Workshops and heat engine laboratory, drawing hall, hydraulics laboratory and boiler house were separately constructed. Shri Gordhanbhai I Patel of M/s Gordhandas Desai &amp; Co was authorized to proceed to Europe and UK to purchase equipment for workshops, laboratories and surveying. The college thus started with the best of the equipment.
                \n \n

         <b><font size='25'>BVM produces a baby - a Search Institute:</font></b> \n
        In 1979, BVM was called upon to establish an institute working entirely for research, development, training and extension work in the area of renewable sources of energy particular for rural  application. Dr. R M Dave took great pains in establishing the Jyoti Solar Energy Institute. The institute(later renamed as Sardar Patel renewable Energy Research Institute) has now developed into a full - fledged institute working independently in the vital area of renewable energy.
            \n\n

        <b><font size='25'>Infrastructure</font></b> \n
        \u2022  Land : 18.96 acres \n
        \u2022  Built up area : 35704.00 sq.m. \n \n

        <b><font size='25'>Outstanding facilities :</font></b> \n
        A spacious hall on the south end of the ground floor of the main building which at one time housed the college library was converted in 1989 into a modern – Auditorium with a capacity of 350 seats and complete with acoustical treatment, light, sound and projection facilities. The Auditorium is beautifully carpeted and curtained and is rated today\' as one of the best Auditorium on Vallabh Vidyanagar campus. /n
        The Mechanical Engineering building has a Conference Room installed with complete audio-visual facilities for a capacity of 40 seats. \n
        The college workshop was reorganized to establish laboratories for the Production Engineering programme and to house new and sophisticated machines. On south side of the workshop a new building has come up for Civil &amp; Production Engineering Laboratories. The building is constructed at a cost of Rs. 40 lakhs . \n
        Principal S B Junnarkar Guest House has a facility of well furnished 10 guest rooms at the second floor of newly constructed Building is constructed with the estimated cost of Rs.60 lakhs is added to BVM infrastructure.
        A Multipurpose Hall with donation from L&amp;T(with the help of CEO Er. Anil Nayak a BVMite) is also an addition to the services of alma mater. \n
        Computer Centers of Civil, Structural, Mathematics and Mechanical Engineering are also available for students and faculties with internet connectivity. \n
        College Canteen and conference room near Principal\'s office have been face lifted during 2006. \n\n

        <b><font size='25'>BVM enters in to IT Era</font></b> \n
        The Computer Center was established in 1985 and is being continuously Upgraded and expanded. Initially it had a UNIX-based minicomputer with Sixteen terminals and a number of PC/XTs and PC/ATs providing DOS Environment. A high resolution work station  with sophisticated software was also available. In addition, the  college installed personal computers in each department to meet the departmental requirements. Currently, college is equipped with approx. 750 computers with good configuration like P4 and above. \n\n

        <b><font size='25'>BVM gets Self-financed mode programs</font></b> \n
        Two more IT related course are now run by BVM. One in 2001-02, 60 seats was approved by AICTE in Information Technology. Second one was also approved by AICTE in academic year 2006-07 with 60 seats in Electronics and Telecommunication. \n
        Recently in 2012, two more existing courses, Mechanical and Production Engineering has been granted 30 seats each in Self-financed Mode by AICTE \n\n

        <b><font size='25'>Affiliations of the College</font></b> \n
          UNIVERSITY PERIOD \n
        \u2022 Bombay University JUNE 1948 - May 1951 \n
        \u2022 Gujarat University JUNE 1951 - May 1957 \n
        \u2022  Sardar Vallabhbhai Vdiyapeeth JUNE 1957 to JUNE 2008 \n
         \u0020 \u0020 \u0020(Re-named as Sardar Patel University from 1966) \n
        \u2022 Gujarat Technological University JUNE 2008 On wards \n\n

         <b><font size='25'>Government Recognition</font></b> \n
        BVM became the grant-in-aid institution of the State Government  in 1958 and slowly grants from the State as well as Central Government started trickling in. The Ministry of Works &amp; Housing  Govenment of India, Started a Rural Housing Wing from 1st January 1959. Principal of BVM,  was named as the Ex-office Director of the Wing. The wing was later renamed as a Regional  Housing Development Center. The Ministry of Urban Development, Government of India recognized BVM in 1984 as one of the centers for training in-service engineers in Environmental Engineering through postgraduate programmed of M E (Environmental Engineering) (the programmed was run by the institute earlier since 1979..) \n\n



    </font>
    </string>


    <string name="placementdetails"> <font style='text-align:justify' color='black' size='20'>
        BVM, a premier engineering college, is considered to be top 1% among all engineering colleges in Gujarat. Since inception, BVM has a record of best Placement all over Gujarat. Around 35+companies, including MNCs like Infosys, Essar, TCS, L&amp;T, ABB, Torrent Power, Seimens, etc.. visit BVM every year for placement. \n\n
        <b><font size='25'>Mr. Mehul Patel \n [I/C Training And Placement]</font></b> \n \n
        <b><font size='25'>Dr. Mehul Shah \n [Assistant Training And Placement]</font></b> \n \n
        <b><font size='25'>Contact:+91 9978997088/ +91 9909529395</font></b>


    </font></string>


    <string name="contactus"><font style='text-align:justify' color='black' size='20'>
            <b>BVM Engineering College</b> , \n Vallabh Vidyanagar - 388120. GUJARAT, INDIA.  \n\n
            Call : 02692-230-104 \n Fax : +91 2692 230762 \n Email : principal@bvmengineering.ac.in \n
        To know more about bvm click the below link: \n


        </font>
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_course__page1">Course_Page1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Graduate Program</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Post Graduate Program</string>

    <string-array name="section_format">
        <item>\u2022 Civil Engineering</item>
        <item>\u2022 Computer Engineering</item>
        <item>\u2022 Electrical Engineering</item>
        <item>\u2022 Electronics Engineering</item>
        <item>\u2022 Mechanical Engineering</item>
        <item>\u2022 Production Engineering</item>
        <item>\u2022 Information Technology (SF)</item>
        <item>\u2022 Electronic &amp; Communication (SF)</item>
        <item>\u2022 Mechanical Engineering (SF)</item>
        <item>\u2022 Production Engineering  (SF)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="section_format1">
        <item>\u2022 Civil Engineering-M. Tech. Environmental Engg. </item>
        <item>\u2022 Civil Engineering-M. Tech. Construction Engg. &amp; Mgt.</item>
        <item>\u2022 Civil Engineering-M. Tech. Structural Engg.</item>
        <item>\u2022 Civil Engineering-M. Tech. Trans. Sys. Engg.</item>
        <item>\u2022 Computer Engineering-M. Tech. Computer Engg.</item>
        <item>\u2022 Electrical Engineering-M. Tech. Electrical Engg.</item>
        <item>\u2022 Mechanical Engineering-M. Tech. Machine Design</item>
        <item>\u2022 Civil Engineering-Infrastructure Engineering and Technology</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="title_activity_main_drawer">main_drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


</resources>
